<resources>
    <!-- General -->
    <string name="app_name">Quake</string>
    <string name="first_letter">Q</string>
    <string name="before_title">Get Prepared</string>
    <string name="after_title">What\'s Next</string>
    <string name="filler">FILLER TEXT</string>
    <!-- Before Page Strings -->
    <string name="kits">Kits</string>
    <string name="shelters">Shelters</string>
    <string name="local_data">Local Data</string>
    <!-- After Page Strings -->
    <string name="flashlight">Flashlight</string>
    <string name="noise">Noise</string>
    <!-- Kits Strings -->
    <string name="kits_basic">Basic</string>
    <string name="kits_medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="kits_ultimate">Ultimate</string>
    <!-- LONG STRINGS -->
    <string name="basic_car">If you are in a moving vehicle, stop as quickly and safely as possible
        and stay in the vehicle. Avoid stopping near or under buildings, trees, overpasses, and
        utility wires. Proceed cautiously once the earthquake has stopped. Avoid roads, bridges, or
        ramps that the earthquake may have damaged.</string>
    <string name="basic_home">Look around places where you spend time.\n
        Identify safe places such as under a sturdy piece of furniture or against an interior wall in your home, office or school so that when the shaking starts you drop to the ground, cover your head and neck with your arms, and if a safer place is nearby, crawl to it and hold on.\n
        Practice how to “Drop, Cover, and Hold On!”\n
        To react quickly you must practice often. You may only have seconds to protect yourself in an earthquake.\n
        Before an earthquake occurs, secure items that could fall and cause injuries (e.g., bookshelves, mirrors, light fixtures).
        Store critical supplies (e.g., water, medication) and documents.\n
        Plan how you will communicate with family members, including multiple methods by making a family emergency communication plan.\n
        When choosing your home or business, check if the building is earthquake resistant per local building codes.\n</string>
    <string name="health_impale">
        Stabilize the object.\n
        This can be done a number of ways, the most popular being wrapping the area around the wound so the object will not wiggle.\n
        However there are alternatives to this, and if you cannot find a bandage stabilizing the object with your other hand works as well.\n
        CLEAN THE WOUND.\n
        This is a critical step in caring for a wound of this nature, as leaving a potentially foreign object within contact of the bloodstream will often lead to infection.\n
        Wrap to prevent blood loss and apply pressure AROUND the wound.\n
        This is where people make the most mistakes since applying pressure directly to the wound may inflict a considerable amount of pain.\n
        Additionally, DO NOT REMOVE THE OBJECT.\n
        Removing an impaled object from the wound may inflict even more blood loss and pain due to the nature of the object.\n
        If you are sure that it is a flat object with no edges for skin to catch on, DO NOT REMOVE IT,\n
        this is because no matter how “sure” you think you are about an object it is always a better idea to let medical professionals take care of the wound.\n
        Monitor yourself for symptoms of shock, these may include vomiting nausea or clammy and cold skin.</string>
</resources>
